Thanks for watching.
Good morning.
Today is the last of Team Eight and the last con of the 9 sisters!
Yay!
Two shows.
You're here.
They're here!
The morning is here.
I was feeling a little sluggish for about an hour yesterday.
Not "hangry" hangry, "hangry" hangry.
We were talking.
Talking?
Talking.
Maybe two hours. We really talked all night.
Yesterday was Yokohama. Yesterday was another concert.
Yes.
I stayed over.
You know...
I didn't want you to come this morning, but you did.
I see.
I have to go to rehearsal.
See you later.
I'll see you later.
Good luck today.
Bye bye.
Here we go.
Seemed like nothing.
Best regards.
Today is the day/night show, which means a concert before 9:00,
We will all be working hard to get the word out,
I look forward to your cooperation.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
How many people will I meet?
A lifetime of love
Tinto.
Sorry, Nagi.
Put this away for everyone.
Everybody.
Eight.
Oh, is that a tinto? Everybody.
Mm-hmm.
Uh, Mike.
Everybody's.
Eight.
Nagi-chan.
I loved it, it hurt, it hurt, my heart's desire
I'll shout it from the center of my heart.
I loved it, it was sad, I hated it
Thank you for watching.
Oh, wait a minute.
Oh!
I'm already done with the humidity from earlier.
My bangs and everything for today.
I straightened them, but now this!
I don't know what to do.
But everyone says I like it better with my hair down.
I'd like to let it down.
Then I'll get ready.
Rehearsal is over.
I'm doing hair and makeup now.
We don't have much time.
We have to start the engine in about an hour.
Eight is always like this.
We rehearse until the last minute.
And then they say, "We only have one hour for makeup.
I'm so glad we only have an hour.
But today was rather good for Eight.
But today's rehearsal went well for Eight, didn't it?
We're done.
I'm looking forward to it!
But, you know, I'm feeling like I have to get ready soon.
But I'm hungry, so I'm eating some bread.
I've got two guys with me, and they're having a great pick time.
Oh, my God.
Did I forget too many outfits?
It's so, so, so hot.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
That's the first one, right?
That's the first one.
The second most?
The second one.
It's the second one.
It's probably the one I've worn the most the whole time.
I miss it. It's so emo.
I left the show with this one, and I was really into the swoosh.
The bangs.
Back then.
I got the bangs done back then.
Okay, here we go.
Ta-da!
LOL!
10 minutes before microwave
I put it on Kumamoto.
Isn't that crazy? Emo.
Why did you take this? That's amazing.
I changed my costume.
This is what I was wearing back then.
She's so young!very young
So young.
I'm going to decorate it. Oh my god, I'm so embarrassed.
Yay!
Oh no, I'm a wreck
My legs and shoulders
It was amazing.
It's not every day you get to operate on two people.
Oh, God, it hurts.
It hurts.
And then...
Interviews with hobbies and toys, etc.
There's a lot more here.
Please check it out!
Thank you very much.
All of you.
Are you there?
Almost there.
Unit block is over.
The bottom member...
Open up.
Kumamoto and Iwamoto-san are coming in.
We did it.
Today.
They were university students.
Let's make it honter, no hassle.
Let's have fun!
Let's go!
Let's start the engine!
Web!
AKB!
Team Raid!
The show is about to start.
It's not good. It's a shadow hole.
I'm off to the shadow hole.
Welcome.
Well, I'll go get ready too.
See you later.
Oh no. Hurry up.
Hello everyone.
I'm your AKB48 teammate, representing Kumamoto prefecture, Narumi Soko.
See you soon! This is Nanami Kurano.
It's starting.
Thank you very much.
Now it's going to start.
I'm off!
Wait!
Everyone!
The day has finally arrived!
We are AKB48 Team Eight!
I'm going!
Let's go!
Let's get the engines running!
AKB Team Eight!
Yeah.
Friend Friend Friend Hey, hang in there.
First time in love
Friend Friend Friend, I'm screaming deep in my heart
I don't even know your name
I don't know your name, but take me with you
LaLaLaLaLaLaLaLa
Miss You Blue in the middle of the month, colorful in the kiln
Dye me in sad colors
Without a clue of goodbye
You said you were waiting for me to forget
I knew no one would come
I can only stay here
Stirring my favorite vegetables
The ceiling slowly descends
Trying to make me forget my tears
The forest of love is one-sided
I'm just gonna walk out and go
Yeah Yeah I love you too much
No No No, I can't stop
yeah yeah end roll
I did it in that outfit.
You haven't done that recently.
You look embarrassed.
You'd think.
I was so excited.
I was more excited than I thought I'd be.
It's different when you're in costume, isn't it?
I put a lot of energy into it.
It was fun.
We got to see each other.
I got to meet you.
Not at all.
We kind of crossed paths.
We were back to back in the same unit.
How was the end roll? I wish I could have seen it.
I mean, we were changing and taking pictures and stuff.
How was the end credit roll?
It was crazy.
I don't know.
I thought it was kind of cool.
I felt like an idiot.
It was definitely cool.That was absolutely cool.
I definitely wanted to see it.
I'll see it later.
Looking forward to it.
I'll put VR in there.
Sure, let's watch it in VR.
Yokoyui Channel.
I love Galta too!
It's been a while.
I'm always active.
I'm rooting for you.
The members, of course.
And of course, I love Planau and Stan.
I will always love you!
LOVE
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
So, Micchi
long time no see
side road
What's a side street now?
We only met on this day.
Did you get to see him today?
I couldn't.
I saw her today.
She's a gal.
She's really a gyaru!
Gal Sato
Gal has become Gal, too!
She's turning into Mi-chan Yumemaru!
She's so cute!
Her bangs are so cute!
So cute!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
She's cute.
It's cute.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Oh, man.
I'm having so much fun.
I've been teasing you too much.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
I'm not gonna change much.
You're so cute.
On your hand.
It's just so original.
Yes, it fits.
I mean, it fits, but it fits.
And you're wearing it wrong here, too.
That's right.
No, it's not.
Yes, it's...
That's right.
No, no, no.
Yes. - No.
No.
Music
Any purity you see up close
A glimmer, a hint, something that won't give up.
The truth that you can't decide, even if you knew it
It's started.
This is what Team Late is all about.
I like it. It's Akaros.
Hold on, hold on.
Akaros.
I couldn't be more excited.
Not now.
Who's there?
I'm leaving.
Have a good day.
Akaros.
Go to Okinawa.
I love Okinawa.
I miss it. Oh, my God.
He's so cute.
What's that? Mike?
Oh, my God, I miss it.
And here we go... the alumni and alumnae will be performing.
Oh, my God, everyone's here.
Akaros is so well known.
The comedy is so goofy.
I can't get enough of the Team Eight feeling!
Adrenaline in the next cycle!
Everyone, the 9 sisters of Eight, it was adrenaline!
KCON 2019.own
I can't sleep.
Oh! I'm just there
Adolescent Ana what?
A girl is always the strongest
There are no empty wordsThere are no empty words
The most extreme betas
Do it and dance, wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah
We will sing with all our hearts and souls
Now please listen to the last song
It's been 10 years
Sakura Hanabi
Somewhere the petals of cherry blossoms
As fireworks and the wind dance in the breeze
See you again in 10 years, I'll be waiting for you at this place
Think more than now
Graduation is a profista, a time of competition
Like that, much more than a love that burns out
Be the fun you are
Somewhere in there.
Thank you very much.
Here it comes. 8, infinity.
I'm surprised. I didn't know this was coming down.
Such a wonderful thing.
Amazing. I want to put it away for safekeeping.
Miracle, thank you very much for coming to the noon boo.
This is Nanami Kurano, the Kumamoto representative of AKB48 Team Eight.
See you at night then!
Thank you for watching!
Good work!
I've been taking pictures all day.
Hey, hey, you're in a lot of pictures.
Hey, hey, you've got a lot of pictures coming.
I'm looking forward to seeing them later.
I'm so happy.
I made a huge mistake. It's really bad.
It's so bad.
Is the noon show over now?
It's over. Thank you for your hard work.
I'm already changing for the night show.
I'm getting ready for the night show,
I'm getting a lot of gifts.
It's amazing. This is great.
This is one of them.
It's the galette I had this morning.
But I'm going to eat it now.
It's great.
There are so many things.
There's so much local food.
Because the O.G. is here.
Yeah.
This one,
I've never seen strawberries from the old treasure house.
How many of them are treated in the same way?
They are amazing strawberries.
Amazing strawberries.
I'll eat it.
Memohamorooma.
The jacket picture of Memohamorooma.
The angle. Memohamorooma.
How do you like it? Strawberry.
Delicious.
This will be handled in a standardized manner.
Treated?
Strawberry is treated like a princess.
Bon appétit.
Memo hamo loomers.
Sweet. I've eaten more than 50 to begin with.
Sweet.
Delicious.
They're good strawberries.
Thank you very much.
I'm so happy.
Let's eat some more.
Bon appétit.
Yes, I'll do some more work and take some more pictures.
When I take pictures,
This is the video that all my teammates love.
We are grateful too.
We are grateful,
I'm sorry I don't have time for this.
Perform a lot,
I hope that everyone will find out how great my teammates and I have been for the past 9 years,
We have all practiced so much,
I hope we can all have a lot of eye contact and enjoy the show to the fullest.
I hope we can all make eye contact and have the best time together.
I'll start the engine now.
Okay, let's go.
Let's go.
Let's start the engine.
Boom, boom, boom!
Ekibee mate!
Thank you for your hard work.
Please help us.
AKB~~~~~
GMA!
Cannes będziese Sub right now!
Good evening.
I'm AKB48 Team 8.
I'm not related to this or that at all.
I don't want to be alone when I leave you.I'm not going to leave you and feel alone.
I don't give a damn about her or the world around me.
It's just another world.
Goodbye
I miss someone so much.
I never thought I'd be here.
I could never have imagined
The future is always you
Before I met my crush Your name is hope
Jim ba bin na wa
Close your eyes and hurry up and breathe The cereal you've been waiting for
I'll kiss you like this, my hands in joyous disorder
Close your eyes and breathe fast I'm falling, the light
I know with you now, now, now, into the dream
No, no, it's fun.
The next song is, you know, the last song that Akimoto-sensei wrote for us before we went on hiatus.
My teammates received 16 original songs,
This song contains the choreography for those 16 songs.
I hope you will pay attention to the choreography.
Please listen to the song.
It's not goodbye
I remember the day we first met
You had a kind of anxious look in your eyes
Turn your head towards my arm
Walk out with confidence
If you ever feel lost
Remember me
Seino! Goodbye Japan!
Ishibashi no Haka (Hill of Stone Bridge)
Someday I'll meet you
If you can find the future
I'll be waiting for you
With a smile
I promise
Thank you for watching
I wonder if there is someone
Will there be anywhere to stop me
In our lifetime
with whom we can talk about our dreams
An irreplaceable being
On a sunny day or a rainy day
No matter what the sky
Under the sky, you'll always be next to me
Tomorrow will always be here
[Applause]
Ai ni nichiwa!
[applause]
Everybody, are you ready?
Please listen. Let's hear it.
Number 47-27.
Giving up. Thinking about someone else.
I've been thinking about someone else.
I want to see you.
Please tell me who it is.
Thank you!
As the title of the teammate is Miracle for 9 years, we have been working together for 9 years.
Fun and happy things.
Keep up the good work!
Thank you.
All the fun, happy, frustrating, and painful things,
Team Eight members have all shared together.
I have a letter for you from someone,
It's beautiful.
Why?
Because Team Eight is you, the members,
In all the fans who have supported you,
in the staff who have supported you,
And of course, it will live on in me.
So, instead of saying goodbye, I send you these words.
Thank you. See you again.
Yasushi Akimoto
Once again, let us all say thank you.
Rescue team, thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work
Thanks to you
Cute
thanks to you
That's great!
Hey, guys, check out that camera.
Yay!
Thanks to you!
Thanks a lot.
Bye bye!
Um, well, Tokunaga-chan.
Yes!
A little toast.
I don't think I've ever taken more.
Please do.
Yes, today, Team Eight is going on hiatus.
I will always love Team Eight!
Cheers!
I'm ready!
So, TERA M A RE COMPANY www.
The concert before the hiatus and the evening session is over!
It's over! Thank you for your hard work!
Thank you for your hard work!
It's over!It's over!
It's over!
I feel so relieved, but I really enjoyed the whole concert!
Yeah! From the opening!
It was so much fun!
I wondered how many people I would be performing with in my lifetime, and I cried at the piano,
It was amazing!
I was thinking about how great it was to be teammates,
I was filled with emotions of how great it was to be teammates and how much fun it was to perform with everyone,
I was so happy to be a part of the concert with all of you.
It was fun to find penlights in the middle of it all!
How was it, Taosan?
I had a lot of fun too,
There were a lot of adults and people who hadn't been to the concert in a while.
There were also a lot of fans who hadn't seen me in quite a while,
I was so happy to know that they have been watching me for a long time!
I was so happy to realize that they have been watching us for a long time! We have been supported by so many people,
I was reminded once again that we have been able to work together as teammates for 9 years with the support of so many people!
Thank you for everything!
Thank you very much!
Although this is the end for us as teammates, we will continue to work hard as AKB48, including NARUTOCHANNEL, in the future,
I will continue to work hard as AKB48, including NARUTOCHANNEL,
Thank you for your continued support!
That's all for now!
Two performances of Team Mate Con!
NARUTOCHANNEL!
Bye bye!
Please subscribe to our channel!